All unique 'Sold To' values in Excel: 194
============================================================

1. 5 Axis International Corporation
2. A Blackstone Energy Corporation
3. ACAA Inc.
4. AME Construction & Gen. Engineering Services
5. AP Renewables Inc.
6. Abda Construction Inc.
7. Abesco Construction Development Corp.
8. Aboitiz Construction Inc.
9. Adam Kennedy Industrial Solutions
10. Aichemy Industrial Controls Engineering Services
11. Amspec Testing Services Pte. Ltd.
12. Anden Construction Company Inc.
13. Andison Manila Use
14. Archonell Inc.
15. Argentech, Incorporated
16. Argotek Innovative Exchange, Inc.
17. Ascof Construction. Inc.
18. Assistco Energy & Industrial Corporation
19. BTSMC Managing Solution Inc.
20. Bolintaguen Cons and Trading Corp.
21. Boskalis Philippines Inc.
22. Brenton Engineered Products Corporation
23. Bureau Veritas S.A.
24. C.M. Pancho Construction, Inc.
25. CBRE GWS IFM Philippines Corporation
26. CIGC Corporation
27. CJI General Services Inc.
28. CPM Construction & Gen. Services Inc.
29. CV Janitorial Maintenance and Utility
30. Chemrez Technologies Inc.
31. Chittick Fire & Security Corporation
32. Chomar Industrial / DMCI
33. Cifra Industrial Services Corporation
34. Cimech Systems Industries, Inc.
35. Constructive Industrial Equipment Trading
36. Coral Bay Nickel Corporation
37. Cutech Process Services Philippines Inc.
38. D.D. Engineering Services
39. D.M. Consunji, Inc.
40. DNV AS Philippine Branch
41. Da-Ri Trenchless Technologies International Corp.
42. Desco Incorporated
43. E E I Corporation
44. EI Construction and Development Corporation
45. Ecolab Philippines
46. Ecology Transport Marine Specialist
47. Energized Industrial Corporation
48. Ernesto
49. Esguerra Shipping Corporation
50. Eunicarl Industrial Sales Corporation
51. Express Waste Solutions, Inc.
52. FEMC International Philippines, Inc.
53. FTPontillo Builders and Engineering Services
54. Fabcon Philippines Inc.
55. Filblast Industrial Trading Corporation
56. Filoil Logistics Corporation
57. First Choice Industrial Safety Corporation
58. First NatGas Power Corporatoon
59. Flagship Petroleum Carriers Inc.
60. Flagship Petroleum Carriers, Inc.
61. Fleet Maintenance and Consultancy Services
62. Fueltek Innovations Inc.
63. Germand Marketing & Industrial Corporation
64. Glenda De Guzman
65. Greenpower Technology Services Inc.
66. HOA's General Construction
67. Harmonic
68. Henkel Philippines Inc.
69. Herma Shipping and Transport Corporation
70. Hydron Corporation
71. I & E Industrial Systems Services
72. Industrial Controls Systems, Inc.
73. Inspecta Inspection Services Corporation
74. JAV Thermal Solutions, Inc.
75. JD Dimalanta Construction Services
76. JGC Philippines Inc.
77. JITS Corporation
78. JX Nippon Philippines Inc.
79. Joel Chavez Construction
80. Josefa Slipways, Inc.
81. KCD Builders Corporation
82. Kapit Bisig Ugnayan Multi-Purpose Cooperative
83. King's Rubber International. Inc.
84. King's Safetynet Inc.
85. Konstrutek Builders and Technical Services, Inc.
86. Kunimori Engineering Works- Manila
87. Kyuten Enterprises
88. LJ Resources Company
89. LS Instrumentation Sales & Services
90. LSI, Inc.
91. Lemery Oil Terminal Corporation
92. Linde Philippines Inc.
93. Linseed Field Corporation
94. Lloyd's Register Asia
95. Lufthansa Technik Philippines, Inc.
96. MHI Power ( Philippines ) Plant Services Corp.
97. MJL Industrial Engineering Services
98. MNS Builders
99. MOOG Controls Corporation - Philippine Branch
100. MRN Techniques & Services
101. MTEC Water Treatment Technologies. Inc.
102. Maibarara Geothermal Inc.
103. Maigue Engineering & Construction Services
104. Measurement and Control Technology, Inc.
105. Mechatrends Contractors Corporation
106. Mecon Systems Services & Maintenance Productions
107. Megatechnip Incorporated
108. Metalite Builders Development Co., Inc.
109. Metrowide Commodities Corporation
110. Mitsubishi Power (Philippines) Inc.
111. Moreta Shipping Lines Inc.
112. Morse Hydraulic System Corporation
113. NC Lanting Security Specialist Agency
114. NPG Worlwide Construction Materials Wholesaling
115. Nagano Services Corporation
116. Nalco Philippines Inc.
117. New Blue Framework Construction Inc.
118. Nikkeru Plant Maintenance
119. Nippon Kaiji Kyokai
120. OSA Industries Philippines Inc.
121. Oleo-Fats, Inc.
122. Olympic Engineering and Sales Corporation
123. On Semiconductor Philippines Corporation
124. PBI
125. PMSI
126. Parsh Marine Services Philippines Inc.
127. Peamkonstrukt Builders & Supply
128. Petron Corporation
129. Phil Gold Processing & Refining Corporation
130. Powerflo Solution Asia Pty. Ltd.
131. Presam Construction and General Services Inc.
132. Prime Metro BMD Corporation
133. Pristine Energy Transfer Corporation
134. QAQ Industrial Instrumentation & Controls
135. RC Avila Construction & Engineering Supplies
136. RTM Industrial Solutions Inc.
137. Ramy Construction Inc.
138. Refletech Engineering Services
139. Reliability & Integrity Management
140. Renato Sagarino
141. Rhajtek Industrial Systems and Construction Inc.
142. Roentgen Separation
143. SAS Builders Corporation
144. SFCS Corporation
145. SGS Philippines Inc.
146. Safeseas Shipping Agency
147. Sakamoto Orient Chemical Corp.
148. Sales record not found
149. Samsung CNT Philippine Corporation
150. San Roque Power Corporation
151. Savior Construction
152. Scientifc Driiling Inc.
153. Seatrium Subic Shipyard, Inc.
154. Shell Pilipinas Corporation
155. Shimizu Philippine Contractors, Inc.
156. Siegwerk
157. Siemens Power Operations Inc.
158. Smart Biz Trading
159. Soil Philippines Index Testing, Inc.
160. Southern J Power Electric, Inc.
161. Sparta Construction Corporation
162. Sta. Clara International Corporation
163. Subic Drydock Corporation
164. Subsea Services Incorporated
165. Swordfish Marine Services Corporation
166. Taganito HPAL Nickel Corporation
167. Tai & Chyun Philippines Inc.
168. Taihei Alltech Construction ( Phils. ) Inc.
169. Taisei - DMCI Joint Venture
170. Technology Exports Services Corp.
171. The Fourth Dimension Inc.
172. Therma Luzon Inc.
173. Three Edz Sandblasting Services
174. Tradetech Marketing
175. Trans World Trading Co., Incorporated
176. Travis General Services Inc.
177. Trescore Industrial Solutiom Corporation
178. UTV Construction & Engineering Services
179. United Perlite Corporation
180. Upholder General Construction & Supply
181. VR Vargas Builders
182. Victoria's Milling
183. Vispet Development Corporation
184. Warranty Replacement
185. Watercorp Technologies
186. World-Tech Marketing Corporation
187. X'former Inc.
188. Yuhantech Philippines, Inc.
189. Zamora Use
190. Zamora display
191. replaced to MCXL-XWHM  SN : KA425-0013916
192. replaced to Ultra Unit SN : 5220ULT01242400142
193. replaced to XT-XWHM  SN MA225-006997
194. to Andison Manila
